Not every item in our basket has to be edible, healthy or chocolaty or anything else in between.
Some of our items are just plain fun for children.
And in this case stuffed animals are a great automatic choice.
You can have them be a bigger bunny, if you have a bigger basket.
Or, maybe your bunny is watching guard over the basket when your little one discovers the basket for the first time.
There is that.
But there a whole bunch of varieties.
You can also have something like this little guy right here.
Look at him.
He could be a cute little guy in your basket hanging out with the chocolate eggs, you know.
So definitely keep in mind having at least a small stuffed animal of some sort.
These often can become collectibles for years to come for children (a very special and cherished childhood memory) that will last much longer than the Easter grass will last, they will last longer than the basket.
They will certainly last longer than anything edible you have in your basket.
These are great keepsakes!
You can find these for sale at a variety of stores.
Of course toy stores (you are going to pay more there); but also a variety of convenience and other stores.
Around Easter you'll start seeing little, cute little bunnies will start popping up everywhere.